<resources>
    <string name="facebook_app_id" translatable="false">1548843298607838</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false">fb1548843298607838</string>

    //admob
    <string name="admob_application_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>

    <string name="app_name">Kallo</string>
    <!--app_title for main navigation & home title-->
    <string name="app_title">Kallo - Hausa Movies &amp; Series</string>
    <string name="app_version">1.0.0</string>
    <string name="contact_email">info@kallo.ng</string>
    <string name="copyright_text">Copyright @ Kallo \nAll right reserved</string>
    <!-- App -->
    <string name="featured_tv_channels">Featured Tv Channel</string>
    <string name="latest_movie">Latest Movies</string>
    <string name="latest_tv_series">Latest Tv Series</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="movie">Movies</string>
    <string name="live_tv">Live TV</string>
    <string name="tv_series">Series</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="genre">Genre</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="no_item_found">No item found</string>
    <string name="cast_n_crew">Cast and Crew</string>
    <string name="signin">Signin</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="director">Director :</string>
    <string name="comments">Comments</string>
    <string name="your_comments">Your Comments</string>
    <string name="add_comments">Add Comments</string>
    <string name="no_internet">No internet connection !</string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="fetch_error">Unable to fetch data</string>
    <string name="login_first">You need to login first</string>
    <string name="comment_empty">Comment can not empty</string>
    <string name="error_toast">Something went wrong ! try later</string>

    <string-array name="nav_item_name">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Series</item>
<!--        <item>Live TV</item>-->
        <item>Genre</item>
<!--        <item>Country</item>-->
        <item>Profile</item>
        <item>Favorite</item>
        <item>Subscription</item>
        <item>Downloads</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>Sign Out</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nav_item_image">
        <item>outline_home_24</item>
        <item>outline_movie_24</item>
        <item>outline_local_movies_24</item>
<!--        <item>outline_live_tv_24</item>-->
        <item>outline_folder_24</item>
<!--        <item>outline_outlined_flag_24</item>-->
        <item>outline_person_24</item>
        <item>outline_favorite_border_24</item>
        <item>ic_subscriptions_black_24dp</item>
        <item>ic_file_download_black_24dp</item>
        <item>outline_settings_24</item>
        <item>outline_lock_24</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="nav_item_name_2">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Series</item>
<!--        <item>Live TV</item>-->
        <item>Genre</item>
<!--        <item>Country</item>-->
        <item>Login</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nav_item_image_2">
        <item>outline_home_24</item>
        <item>outline_movie_24</item>
        <item>outline_local_movies_24</item>
<!--        <item>outline_live_tv_24</item>-->
        <item>outline_folder_24</item>
<!--        <item>outline_outlined_flag_24</item>-->
        <item>outline_lock_24</item>
        <item>outline_settings_24</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- payment related to Settings -->
    <!--PayPal accepted currency-->
    <string-array name="paypal_currency_list">
        <item>USD</item>
        <item>AUD</item>
        <item>BRL</item>
        <item>GBP</item>
        <item>CAD</item>
        <item>CZK</item>
        <item>DKK</item>
        <item>EUR</item>
        <item>HKD</item>
        <item>HUF</item>
        <item>ILS</item>
        <item>JPY</item>
        <item>MXN</item>
        <item>TWD</item>
        <item>NZD</item>
        <item>NOK</item>
        <item>PHP</item>
        <item>PLN</item>
        <item>RUB</item>
        <item>SGD</item>
        <item>SEK</item>
        <item>CHF</item>
        <item>THB</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--search range-->
    <string name="year_range_start">1900</string>
    <string name="year_range_end">2020</string>

    <!-- Example General settings -->

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->

    <string name="title_activity_item_show">ItemShowActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">DetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reply">ReplyActivity</string>
    <string name="program_guide">Program Guide</string>
    <string name="live">Live</string>
    <string name="watching_on">Watching live on</string>
    <string name="all_tv_channel">All TV Channels</string>
    <string name="you_may_also_like">You may also like</string>
    <string name="dark_mode">Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="tv_channels">Tv Channels</string>
    <string name="watching_catch_up_tv">Watching Catch-up TV</string>
    <string name="deactive_account_text">If you do not want to use this account you can de-active easily.</string>
    <string name="reason_to_deactivate_account">Reason to deactivate account</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>

    <string name="terms_condition_text">
        PRIVACY STATEMENT\n \n
This Privacy Statement explains our practices, including your choices, regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of certain information, including your personal information in connection with the Kallo TV entertainment and streaming Service.
Introduction
Welcome to KalloTV (The Platform). The Platform is operated and controlled by Spacekraft Media Limited (KalloTV we or us). This Privacy Policy Statement sets out how KalloTV and its holding, related and subsidiary companies, collect, store and handle personal information for users on our Platform. We respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy.
Consent
Under data protection laws, we are required to provide you with certain information about who we are, how we process your personal data and for what purposes, and your rights in relation to your personal data. This information is provided in this Privacy Policy Statement and it is important that you read that information.
By accepting this privacy policy, you have given us your consent to our processing of your personal data (including your name, contact details, financial and device information) as described in the policy. You also consent to our processing of your location Data including details of your current location disclosed by GPS technology so that location-enabled Services are activated. We are committed to protecting your personal data and respecting your privacy.
How you can withdraw consent
Once you provide consent, you may change your mind and withdraw consent at any time by contacting us at support@Kallo.ng but that will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent.
\nIntroduction\n
This policy applies to all users of KalloTVs services anywhere in the world, including users of KalloTV Apps, Websites, Service Sites, features or other services unless covered by a separate privacy policy statement and particularly, the following:
• KalloTV App mobile application software (App), once you have downloaded or streamed a copy of the App onto your mobile telephone or handheld device (Device).
• Any of the services accessible through the App (Services) that are available on the App Site or other sites of ours (Services Sites).
This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.
This App is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children. Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

Important information and who we are\n
KalloTV Limited is the controller and is responsible for your personal data (referred to as Company, we, us or our in this policy).
Contact details
Our full details are:
Full name of legal entity: Spacekraft Media Limited
Email address: support@Kallo.ng
Postal address: c/o Edoigiawerie and Company, 126 Association Road, Dolphin Estate, Ikoyi,
Lagos, Nigeria.
Telephone: You can also chat live or call us using the live chat icon in red
Changes to the privacy policy and your duty to inform us of changes
We keep our privacy policy under regular review.
This version was last updated on November, 2021. It may change and if it does, these changes will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you when you next start the App or log onto one of the Services Sites. The new policy may be displayed on-screen and you may be required to read and accept the changes to continue your use of the App or the Services.
It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during our relationship with you.
Third party links
Our Sites may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. Please note that these websites and any services that may be accessible through them have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any personal data that may be collected through these websites or services, such as Contact and Location Data. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites or use these services.
The data we collect about you
We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you as follows: Identity Data.
Contact Data.
Financial Data.
Transaction Data.
Device Data.
Content Data.
Profile Data.
Usage Data.
Marketing and Communications Data. Location Data
We explain these categories of data under Description of categories of personal data below.
We also collect, use and share Aggregated Data such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data could be derived from your personal data but is not considered 6
\n\n\n
personal data in law as this data will not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific App feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy policy.
We do not collect any Special Categories of Personal Data about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health, and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.
How is your personal data collected?
We will collect and process the following data about you:
Information you give us. This is information (including Identity, Contact, Financial, and Marketing and Communications Data) you consent to giving us about you by filling in forms on the App Site and the Services Sites (together Our Sites), or by corresponding with us (for example, by email or chat or telephone call) or by visiting any of our offices. It includes information you provide when you register to use the App Site, download or register an App, subscribe to any of our Services, search for an App or Service, make an in-App purchase, make a feedback to us, enter a competition, promotion or survey, and when you report a problem with an App, our Services, or any of Our Sites. If you contact us, we will keep a record of that correspondence.
Information we collect about you and your device. Each time you visit one of Our Sites or use one of our Apps we will automatically collect personal data including hardware models, device IP address, operating systems and versions, software, preferred languages, unique device identifiers, advertising identifiers, serial numbers, device motion data, content and usage data. We collect this data using cookies and other similar technologies.
Location Data. We also use GPS technology to determine your current location. Some of our location-enabled Services require your personal data for the feature to work. If you wish to use the particular feature, you will be asked to consent to your data being used for this purpose.
Information we receive from other sources including third parties and publicly available sources. We will receive personal data about you from various third parties and public sources as set out below:
Device Data from the following parties:
• analytics providers;
• advertising networks;
• search information providers;
• Contact, Financial and Transaction Data from providers of technical,
payment and delivery services;
• Identity and Contact Data from data brokers or aggregators; and
• Identity and Contact Data from publicly available sources;

\n\n
Trademarks
The Kallo TV Logo and brand collaterals are trademarks of Spacekraft Media Limited.
If you havent received our permission, do not use our marks as your own or in any manner that implies sponsorship or endorsement by Kallo TV.
A product branded with our name or logo is a reflection of Kallo TV. Unless you are one of our licensees, we don’t allow others to make, sell, or give away anything with our name or logo on it.
Copyright
The copyrights in the shows and movies on our service are owned by the producers, including Spacekraft Media Limited. If you believe your or someone else’s copyrights are being infringed upon through the service, let us know through our contact service.
Cookies
We use cookies or other tracking technologies to distinguish you from other users of the App, App Site, the distribution platform (Appstore and Play Store) or Services Sites and to remember your preferences. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you use the App or browse any of Our Sites and also allows us to improve the App and Our Sites.
How we use your personal data
We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to do so. Most commonly we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:
• Where we need to perform the Services you have engaged us for.
• To help us monitor and improve our performance and Services, our customer relations teams and service providers and the App and to make these more
efficient.
• To maintain and develop our business systems and infrastructure, including testing
and upgrading of these systems.
• To manage staff training and quality assurance.
• To notify you about benefits and changes to the features of our Services.
• To determine how can we improve services to you.
• Where you have consented before the processing.
• Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your
interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
• Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.
We will only send you direct marketing communications by email or text if we have your consent. You have the right to withdraw that consent at any time by contacting us.
We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any third party for marketing purposes.

    </string>
    <string name="deactivate_account">Deactivate Account</string>
    <string name="explore_by_genre">Explore By Genre</string>
    <string name="explore_by_country">Explore By Country</string>
    <string name="share_this_app">Share This App</string>
    <string name="share_body">I would like to share Kallo App.  Here you can download this from playstore :\n    https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=</string>
    <string name="term_of_services">Term of Services</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="account_deactivate_info"><![CDATA[Your account will be deactivate & only admin can activate again.]]></string>
    <string name="regular_program">Regular Program</string>
    <string name="international">International</string>
    <string name="server">Server</string>
    <string name="_1080p">1080P</string>
    <string name="dummy_name">Jhon Doe</string>
    <string name="notifications">NOTIFICATIONS</string>
    <string name="push_notification">Push Notification</string>
    <string name="others">OTHERS</string>
    <string name="no_data_found">No data found.</string>
    <string name="no_subscription_history">No subscription history found.</string>
    <string name="plan">Plan</string>
    <string name="upgrade_membership">Upgrade Membership</string>
    <string name="p_date">P.Date</string>
    <string name="from">From</string>
    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="wallet">Wallet</string>
    <string name="fund_wallet">Fund Wallet</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>


    <string name="paid_content">You are trying to watch a paid content. Please subscribe a plan first.</string>
    <string name="subscription_required">Subscription Required</string>
    <string name="subscribe_text">Subscribe</string>
    <string name="payment_success">Payment Success.</string>
    <string name="subscribe_error">To subscribe a plan, you have to login first.</string>
    <string name="something_went_text">Something went wrong, try again or contact to your developer.</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="downloading">Downloading</string>
    <string name="download_completed">Download Completed</string>
    <string name="watch_now">Watch Now</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="select_server">Select Server</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="all_kids_videos">All Kids Videos</string>
    <string name="all_tv_series">All TV Series</string>
    <string name="unlimited_movies">Unlimited Movies</string>
    <string name="please_select_your_payment_method">Please select your payment method</string>
    <string name="download_appear_text">Your download item will be appear here.  Download item not found.</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="searcHError_message">Title Or Type can\'t be empty</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="instruction_3">3. Then click on "Connect To TV."</string>

    <!-- dialog instruction -->
    <string name="dialog_instruction_1">1. Go to your </string>
    <string name="dialog_instruction_2"> app in your phone. </string>
    <string name="dialog_instruction_3">2. Buy a package </string>
    <string name="continue_browsing">Continue browsing</string>
    <string name="type_keyword">Type keyword</string>
    <string name="year_range">Year Range</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="tv_category">TV Category</string>
    <string name="all_countries">All Countries</string>
    <string name="all_categories">All Categories</string>
    <string name="external_download">External Download</string>
    <string name="inApp_download">In App Download</string>
    <string name="all_genres">All Genres</string>
    <string name="download_not_permitted">You must have subscription to download this video.</string>
    <string name="file_already_downloaded">File already downloaded.</string>
    <string name="file_not_found">File not found</string>
    <string name="phone_number_with_country_code">Phone number (with country code)</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="user_name_">User Name:</string>
    <string name="active_plan_">Active Plan:</string>
    <string name="email_">Email:</string>
    <string name="expire_date_">Expire Date:</string>
    <string name="active_subscription">Active Subscription</string>
    <string name="no_download_server_found">No download link found</string>
    <string name="no_video_found">No video found</string>
    <string name="failed_to_communicate">Failed to communicate with server. \nPlease check your Internet configuration</string>
    <string name="no_configuration_data_found">No configuration data found.</string>
    <string name="please_login_first_to_see_favorite_list">Please login to see favorite list.</string>


</resources>
